https://www.wdhospital.org/wdh/about-wdh/site-policies

VISITOR RESTRICTIONS IN PLACE. Visit link for details and more updates.
Search WDH
What are you looking for?
Patient Portal
Log In As...
Provider Search
Search for doctors, nurse practitioners, physician assistants and nurse midwives on the medical staff at Wentworth-Douglass Hospital and/or Wentworth Health Partners.
Specialty
APRN- Thoracic SurgeryAPRN-GastroenterologyAPRN-General SurgeryAPRN-Gerontology Primary CareAPRN-NeonatalAllergy/ImmunologyAnesthesiologyBariatric SurgeryBehavioral HealthCardiac ElectrophysiologyCardiologyCertified Nurse MidwifeCertified Registered Nurse AnesthetistClinical GeneticsCritical Care MedicineDentistryDermatologyEmergency MedicineEndocrinologyFamily MedicineGastroenterologyGeneral SurgeryGenetic CounselingGynecologic OncologyGynecologyHematology-OncologyHospital MedicineHyperbaric MedicineInfectious DiseaseInternal MedicineLicensed Clinical Mental Health CounselorLicensed Independent Clinical Social WorkerLicensed Marriage and Family TherapistMaster Licensed Alcohol and Drug CounselorMedical OncologyNeonatal-PerinatalNephrologyNeurologyNeurosurgeryOb-GynOphthalmologyOral SurgeryOrthopedic SurgeryOrthopedicsOtolaryngologyPA-C- Hospital MedicinePA-C-GastroenterologyPA-C-Medical OncologyPain MedicinePalliative MedicinePathologyPediatric CardiologyPediatric DentistryPediatric EndocrinologyPediatric GastroenterologyPediatric NephrologyPediatric PulmonologyPediatricsPhysical Medicine & RehabilitationPlastic SurgeryPodiatristPre-Admission ServicesPrimary CarePsychiatric/Mental HealthPsychiatryPsychologyPulmonary MedicineRadiation OncologyRadiologyRheumatologySleep MedicineSports MedicineSurgical OptimizationThoracic SurgeryUrgent CareUrologyVascular SurgeryWound Care
Choose Provider Group
All Providers
Wentworth Health Partners
Massachusetts General Hospital
Language
ArabicBengaliChineseCzechEnglishFilipinoFrenchGermanHindiIndonesianItalianKoreanMandarin ChineseMarathiPolishRussianSpanishTagalogTamilTurkishUkrainian
Physician Verification Lookup
Pathology
Robert R. Cawley, D.O.
Dover, NH 03802
Education & Training
Board Certification
See Profile
Main Menu
Patient Portal
Donate Now
About WDH
Patient Portal
Log In As...
Wentworth-Douglass Hospital
Wentworth Health Partners
Seacoast Cancer Center
Learn More
Main Menu
Patient Portal
Donate Now
About WDH
About Wentworth-Douglass
About WDHLocations & DirectionsLeadership & BoardHistoryQuality & SafetyMassachusetts General HospitalSeacoast Healthcare InitiativeAffiliationsAwards & RecognitionsGiving BackSupport UsWebsite PolicySocial Media AgreementContact UsBienvenidoSelamat Datang
Web Privacy Policy
Wentworth-Douglass Hospital is committed to protecting your privacy.  We have created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect certain information about you when you use this website, and how we protect the privacy of that information. This Policy does not apply to your personal health information.
Information We Collect and How We Use It
Two types of information are collected from our website:
Personal or "individually identifiable" information you provide to us.
Aggregate information regarding overall website traffic patterns.
We will not disclose, sell or rent your name or any personal information about you to any third party.  We use the aggregate information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different pages and sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. The aggregate information we collect is not linked to personal information, and we do not report on individual user sessions.  Personal InformationYou do not need to give personal information to receive information from this site. There are instances online, however, when the Hospital requests individually identifiable information from you. We may retain this information for processing and to facilitate requests. Information you submit to us is treated in the same confidential manner as information you might provide in a written format such as an application or donation form.Online DonationsWhen you choose to make an online donation to the Wentworth-Douglass Foundation through our website, we may request the following information: (i) Contact information: first and last name, street address, city, province or state, postal or zip code, country, telephone number, e-mail address and other contact information. This information is used to process your donation and your tax receipt. (ii) Credit card information: We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to offer safe and secure credit card and electronic check transactions for our customers. The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card and electronic check processing networks (see an online payments diagram). The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including:
128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions.
Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information.
Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard.
For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.NetPrivacy Policy.(iii) Refund Policy:  Donations to the Wentworth-Douglass Foundation are not refundable.E-mail Inquiries Our website contains several e-mail links that allow web visitors to easily send an e-mail inquiry or feedback to Wentworth-Douglass Hospital. Examples include e-mail inquiries to specific departments at the Hospital. When you use the e-mail links, your e-mail address and the subject of your inquiry are provided to the department to respond to your specific request only.
Cookies In order to improve our site on an ongoing basis, we use cookies to track your visit. Wentworth-Douglass Hospital also may use cookies to provide users with certain features available on our website.A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the website that gave it to you.  It functions as your identification card.  It is not a program and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie – this gives you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can use the Hospital website without cookies, but you may have to re-enter information each time you visit. Links to Other Sites and ServicesWentworth-Douglass Hospital is not responsible for the contents of any linked website, any link contained in a linked website or any changes or updates to such websites.  We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that requests personal information from you.
Effect of Policy By visiting the Wentworth-Douglass Hospital Privacy Policy online, you are accepting the practices described in this notice.  Despite the measures described in this Policy, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from us via this web page or the Internet cannot be guaranteed.  Wentworth-Douglass Hospital reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.  Our Policy will be kept up-to-date and posted on our website.
Click to Activate
Contact Us
Wentworth-Douglass Hospital
789 Central Avenue
Dover, New Hampshire 03820
Phone: (603) 742-5252
See All Locations
Find a Provider
Search for providers associated with Wentworth-Douglass Hospital.
Find Now
What's Happening?
Check out our upcoming community events.
View Events
Living Well Seacoast
Healthy tips and information from Wentworth-Douglass experts on our blog.
Read More
Subscribe to our newsletter.
Sign up to receive occasional emails about Wentworth-Douglass news and events.
